welcome to ICICI Prudential reading
right you are watching a video on
features of your online account for your
ICICI Prudential health insurance
policies to explore service options to
your online account visit ICICI through
life.com click on login login as
customer once logged them even land on
my dashboard page the important messages
related to your policies can be seen in
alerts and notifications section you can
see a snapshot of your policies in my
policy section to know more about your
policies you can click on my policies
tab click on the policies for which you
need more information all the relevant
information about your policy is
available on this page from your
dashboard you can directly access
important services from Quick Links
section or you can click on transactions
tab for more services you can easily do
all the relevant transactions from the
switch on your own you can download all
the relevant policy statements from the
statements page you can also update your
personal details very easily from my
profile page so go ahead and log into
your ICICI pro-life account and explore
all the servicing options that you get
available online thank you